<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reviews on Cynosure</title>
    <link>http://Cynsosure.page/reviews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reviews on Cynosure</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-nz</language><atom:link href="http://Cynsosure.page/reviews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Landfill Majority with Pamela Hancock</title>
      <link>http://Cynsosure.page/reviews/2022-02-25-pamela-hancox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Cynsosure.page/reviews/2022-02-25-pamela-hancox/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps I’m too youong to geth the humour, maybe it went way over my head and I’m going to look like a fool as soon as I publish this. I now understand the bravery it requires to get on stage with that as your set. I can see myself enjoying this around a dinner with friends and family, as everyone is a little drunk and full, and only half paying attention.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hole Review</title>
      <link>http://Cynsosure.page/reviews/2021-11-28-hole/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Cynsosure.page/reviews/2021-11-28-hole/</guid>
      <description>Written by Lynda Chanwai-Earle Directed by Kerryn Palmer and Sally Richards Music Composed by Gareth Farr Starring Sepe Mua’au, Stevie Hancox-Monk, and Elle Wootton Viewed on 28/11/2021
 I wasn’t really sure what I was in for when I saw Hole. What I got was a rich exploration of the way personal relationships can spill into the wider world. The play follows Stella, an atmospheric scientist investigating the recent ozone hole.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Illegally Blind Review</title>
      <link>http://Cynsosure.page/reviews/2022-01-10-illegally-blind/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://Cynsosure.page/reviews/2022-01-10-illegally-blind/</guid>
      <description>The line &amp;#39;A token effort has been made to include the abled as well’ appears in the marketing material, I believe this is what they intended. Alas, this like most of the show falls flat. The story follows Susan as they navigate their life dealing with bigotry in all forms. In doing so it asks able bodied audiences to not be cunts, to show that the minorities are in fact people who are working their hardest, and need to be empowered.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
